ok-magazine.com 2008-04-12

# OK! Magazine - Privacy

## PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for okmagazine.com. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to �OK!� include okmagazine.com and Northern & Shell North America Limited. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning assigned to them in the okmagazine.com Terms and Conditions of Use. 

OK! is committed to your right to privacy and will use your data only as set forth in our Privacy Policy below. Please read this information carefully. By using the Site you agree to our collecting and using your personal information as described below. 

Though the Privacy Policy below has been developed to take account of the rapid development of Internet technology it is subject to change. Any such changes will be announced on this page. 

1\. What Is Covered By These Provisions? 

2\. What Information Do We Collect About You And How Do We Use It? 

3\. How Do I Correct Or Update My Information? 

4\. How Do I Opt Out From Receiving E-mails? 

5\. What Is The Policy Regarding Member to Member Communications? 

6\. How Is My Information Protected? 

7\. How Will Changes In This Policy Be Announced? 

8\. Any Queries? 

What Is Covered By These Provisions? 

This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected by OK! on the okmagazine.com website. 

OK! contains links to other sites. OK! is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policy of each website they visit that collects personally identifiable information. 

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post information in blogs, message boards or other public forums, that information can be accessed and used by the public, for example to send you unsolicited communications. OK! IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY USE MADE OF INFORMATION VOLUNTARILY POSTED IN ANY OK! FORUM OR OTHER PUBLIC PLACE. 

What Information Do We Collect About You And How Do We Use It? 

The information we may gather falls into two categories: 1) personal information you voluntarily supply when you subscribe, order, complete a survey, register with our Site, post information in an OK! Forum, enter a contest or provide your e-mail address; and 2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our Site. 

Personally Identifiable Information 

OK! collects information about you when you register to use the Service, such as your name, e-mail address, zip code, gender and other information. If you agree to participate in an optional survey, or register for optional sweepstakes, contests or special offers, we may also collect other information that you provide or post in an OK! Forum. 

At times, we will offer services or products for purchase. To enable such purchases, we collect and store billing and credit or debit card information. This information will be shared only with third parties who perform tasks required to complete the purchase transaction, such as fulfilling orders and processing credit card information. 

We may use the personal information that you provide during registration to send you updates, breaking news, newsletters or news regarding the service. You may choose not to receive e-mails of this type by going to your My OK! page, selecting Edit Your Profile, and following the instructions that are given. We may also use this information to send you copies of OK! Magazine that you request. 

For personal information that you provide to us at times other than at registration, such as for a promotion or registration for a sweepstakes, at the time of collection we will state to whom, if anyone, that information is being provided. 

We will not sell your personal information to direct marketing companies or other such organizations, and we will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your e-mail address or any other personally identifiable information without your permission. From time to time, OK! may allow a limited number of companies to send users promotional e-mails, if we believe, in our discretion, that the products or services promoted are something that our users might enjoy. 

Tracking Information 

OK! logs non-personally-identifiable information, including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the Site. When you use the Site we may automatically issue your computer with a small piece of code (a "Cookie"). Cookies are files we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We can use Cookies to show us how you are using our Site and to collect demographic or statistical information about user behavior. OK! may also use other devices, such as Clear Gifs or Web Beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information. These devices allow us to analyze the popularity of the Site and to better manage and improve the service we provide to you, as well as to provide a varied selection of advertisements based upon your usage. 

Non-personally-identifiable data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This information may be shared with third-parties, for purposes including providing more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are also recorded for security and monitoring purposes. 

You may also be issued with a Cookie or other tracking device from our advertisers. Advertisers� use of Cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, which may differ from the OK! Privacy Policy. 

Other Uses 

Except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, OK! will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we are acting: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by OK!, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the OK! Terms and Conditions of Use, (3) to protect our rights or property; or (4) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the Service. 

OK! reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of OK! or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

Children�s Guidelines 

OK! does not knowingly collect or store any information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. 

How Do I Correct Or Update My Information? 

You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by going to your My OK! page, selecting Edit Your Profile, and following the instructions that are given. 

How Do I Opt Out From Receiving E-mails? 

If you no longer wish to receive updates or notifications from OK! you may choose not to by going to your My OK! page, selecting Edit Your Profile, and following the instructions that are given. 

What Is The Policy Regarding My OK! Member Communications? 

My OK! members can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. OK! stores the email addresses that members provide to facilitate member to member communications. My OK! members may also store email addresses of people they know in their My OK! page and may choose to send invitations and other communications to those addresses. 

You may prevent My OK! email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject "BLOCK" to privacy@okmagazine.com. Please note that the email must come from the account you wish to block. 

How Is My Information Protected? 

Users� accounts are secured by user-created passwords. OK! takes precautions to ensure that user account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect user information that is stored within our database. 

PLEASE NOTE THAT OK! CANNOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION. UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY OR USE, HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE FAILURE, AND OTHER FACTORS MAY COMPROMISE THE SECURITY OF MEMBER INFORMATION AT ANY TIME. 

How Will Changes In This Policy Be Announced? 

From time to time we may make changes to our Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will post them on the Site. This way, you can stay aware of any changes, what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy after those changes have been posted. However, if we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from and inconsistent with the manner stated at the time of collection, we will post a notice on the Site for 30 days prior to the change taking effect. During this 30-day period, you will be able to remove your personally identifiable information from our database. After such 30-day period, you will be bound to the revision, regardless of the time the information was collected. 

Any Queries? 

If you have any queries or concerns about privacy on the Site, please contact us at: privacy@okmagazine.com or Privacy Policy Manager, OK! Magazine, Northern & Shell North America Limited, 475 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY 10017, USA.
